- Hello . - Hey , I 'm on my way .
- And don 't forget my money . - See you soon .
- And , Bailey , don 't you forget .
Shit .
- Shit !
- Jesus !
Cool .
Well , hello , dolly .
ő What are you thinking about ő
ő Who do you think you are ő
ő Oh , rage in the cage and piss upon the stage ő
ő There 's only one sure way to bring the giant down ő
ő Defunct the strings of cemetery things ő
ő We 're one flat foot on the devil 's wings ő
ő Crawl on me sink into me ő
ő Die for me living dead girl ő
ő What are you thinking about ő
ő Who do you think you are ő
ő Oh , raping the geek and hustling the freak ő
ő Like a hunchback juice on a sentimental noose ő
ő Operation filth , they love to love the wealth ő
ő Of an S.S. whore making scary sounds ő
ő Crawl on me sink into me ő
ő Die for me living dead girl ő
ő Ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo ő
ő What are you thinking about ő
ő Aw , crawl on me sink into me ő
ő Die for me living dead girl ő
ő Blood on her skin ő
ő Dripping with sin ő
ő Do it again ő
ő Living dead girl ő ő
Hello . I 'm Chief Kincaid , Jade 's uncle .
- David Collins . Nice to meet you , sir . - David , come on in .
Jade !
David 's here !
I 've been hearing good things about you , David . You 're off to Princeton next fall .
Yes , sir .
- What are you going to study ? - Theater Arts .
Mm-hmm . But on an athletic scholarship , right ? Playing hockey ?
Figure skating .
Mm-hmm . Jade !
Warren , don 't scream .
Hi .
You look great .
Jade , uh , I have to tell you . This guy is a big improvement over the last one .
- I think your mother and father would 've agreed . - My parents liked all my friends .
I 'll be home by midnight .
She 's in good hands , sir .
Uh ... You forget something ?
Oh . This is for you .
- I love lilies . - Actually , it 's an orchid . Uh , cymbidium orchid ?
You put it in a vase and drop an aspirin in the water ,
it should last you the whole week .
Or so I read . Nice meeting you .
She just left .
- You look beautiful .
ő ő [ Rock ]
- So Warren fell for it ? - Mm-hmm .
David made quite an impression . I think Warren 's in love .
Yuck . Not my type .
I 'm so over that whole uniform thing .
ő I won 't go home now , mama Don 't make a fool of me ő
ő You see , I am the boogie-woogie- - ő
- Christ. it 's Needlenose .
Gotcha .
[ Chanting ]
Give me the power , I beg of you .
Awake !
Awake ! Awake ! Awake ! Awake !
What a crock .
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Knocking At Door ]
- Hey , Tiffany . - What are you doing here ?
Come on . Let me in . I 'll catch my death out here .
Promises , promises .
Whoa . Whoo ! Hey , how was your day ?
Same old , same old .
- Oh , hey , check it out . - What ?
- Check it out . - What is it ?
- You mean who is it ? - Who is it ?
You mean who was it .
Oh , my God .
Oh , my God . You really did a number on him , didn 't you ?
What did you use ? Was it really bloody ? Did he scream a lot ?
Was he ha- -
You know , Damien , this guy looks awfully familiar .
I recognize the nail polish .
- Shit . - You never really actually killed anybody , did you ?
Did you ? Did you ? You pathetic worm !
Come on , Tiff . I 'm working up to it .
Aw , man .
You know , it took me ten hours to make that thing .
- Damien . - Yeah ?
Could you do me a favor ...
and see if my lipstick is under the sofa there ?
Ah , ah , ah , ah , ah . Back on your knees .
Crawl .
Good boy .
Stay down on the floor where you belong .
That 's right .
There 's nothing under here .
Charlotte .
- How did you get out ? Tsk , tsk , tsk , tsk , tsk .
Oh !
Ugh !
- Tiffany .
Well , here we are .
How long have we been going out for now , huh ?
What ?
- Don 't you think you 've kept me waiting long enough ? - No .
Oh .
You know what the French call an orgasm ?
- Le petit morte .
" The little death . "
Come on , Tiffany . Let 's die a little .
Ah !
Hi . I 'm Chucky . Wanna play ?
- Where the hell did you get this thing ? - Got him from the cops .
He 's the actual doll from those murders . I stitched him together .
- You got to be kidding me . - No , I 'm not kidding you . Why would I kid you ?
- I knew you were obsessed , but ... Chucky ? He 's so ' 80s . - I 'm not ob- -
- He isn 't even scary . - No , he 's not . Yes , he is .
What are you looking at , punk ?
All right . So , I was wrong .
I thought he 'd make an ... interesting toy .
- Damien ? - Huh ?
You wanna play ?
Okay .
First , I do this .
Are you ready for a menage a trois ?
- What 's that ? - I thought you understood French .
- Ow ! Oh-ho !
Now you watch me .
Both of you .
You know , Damien , there 's something I never told you about Chucky .
- Don 't tell me Schmucky is one of those dolls who wets his pants . - Ah , ah , ah , ah , ah .
I wouldn 't talk that way about Chucky if I were you .
He has a very bad temper .
- Ooh ! - You see , we lived together for years .
Of course , that was before the cops killed him .
That was before he passed his soul into that doll there .
Boy , was he ever jealous .
Anybody even looked at me , Chucky would take care of him .
Wouldn 't you , Chucky ?
We were gonna get married .
God , was he an incredible lover .
- He was the best I ever had . - Come on , baby .
He ain 't big enough to take care of a woman like you .
It ain 't the size that counts , asshole . It 's what you do with it .
All right .
Hi .
- How you been ? - Okay .
- You ? - Peachy .
Actually , to tell you the truth , I 've been kinda out of it .
I know . It took me ten years to find you .
That is sick .
What are you doing with this jerk anyway ?
Ten years is a long time , Chucky .
Besides , I was never actually with him .
You know me .
I 'll kill anybody , but I 'll only sleep with someone I love .
- You look great , Tiff . - Thanks .
I mean it . I gotta be honest .
I always thought you were gonna let yourself go .
Come here .
Yeah .
Huh ?
Stop it .
- Hmm .
All right , you satisfied ?
- Can I wait in the car , please ? - No .
[ Siren Chirps ]
All right , Boogie Nights , you 're up .
This is such a load of shit .
You know we haven 't been drinking .
Well , then , you 've got nothing to worry about , do you ?
Evening , Chief .
Seems like a false alarm here .
That 's okay , Norton . Better safe than sorry , right ?
- This is a new low . - For you too .
- Get in the car . - Bite me .
Jade , when you 're 18 , you can go to hell for all I care .
But until then , I 'm stuck with you .
And I 'll be damned if I 'm gonna let you embarrass me ...
by ending up on Jerry Springer with some trailer trash lowlife .
- You fuck . - But you won 't .
Not Jade anyway . Not anymore .
In the car .
You can 't keep us from seeing each other .
I 'm the Chief of Police , sport . I can do whatever I want .
So if , for example , I was to run a blood test on you tonight ...
and the results made you look like Christian Slater on New Year 's Eve ,
you think anybody would question me ?
- He 's bluffing . - Try me .
I wish we really could choose our own families .
David , you keep your orchid dry now , you hear ?
- Come on , sunshine .
" Try me . "
Screw him .
If I were you , I would take Jade , get the hell outta Dodge ...
and never look back .
Look , Chucky .
I made Swedish meatballs , your favorite .
Honey , you shouldn 't have .
Well , I wanted everything tonight to be absolutely perfect .
Tiff , what the hell is that ?
It 's a playpen , silly , for the nursery .
You know , Chucky , I still have the ring .
- What ring ? - The ring , the one you left for me .
I found it on the mantel the night you were killed . I 've never taken it off .
Oh , that ? The one I got from Vivian Van Pelt .
- Vivian who ? - Vivian Van Pelt .
I dumped her in the river , remember ?
That ring is worth five or six grand , easy .
You mean ... . you weren 't gonna ask me to marry you ?
What are you , fucking nuts ?
You thought- -
You haven 't changed .
You 'll never change .
What the hell was I thinking ?
Now , the first thing we gotta do is get me outta this body once and for all .
No .
I think I prefer you like this .
You 're kinda cute . You 're just like a little baby .
- Is the little baby ticklish ? Is he ? - Stop !
- Is he ? Is he ? Is he ? - Stop ! Stop !
- Is he ? Is he ? Okay . Mommy 's tired .
Time to go to sleep .
Okay , I get it .
You 're still hung up on the domestic thing .
No problem . We 'll get hitched .
Sorry . I 'm not into short guys .
My mother always said love was supposed to set you free .
But that 's not true , Chucky .
I 've been a prisoner of my love for you for a very long time .
Now it 's payback time .
You let me outta here right now !
Sweet dreams , asshole .
ő I 'm crazy ő
ő Crazy for feelin so blue ő
ő I knew ő
ő You 'd love me as long as you wanted ő
ő And someday ő
ő You 'd leave me for somebody new ő
ő Crazy for tryin ' ő
ő And crazy for cryin ' ő
ő And I 'm crazy for lovin ' you ő
ő I 'm crazy for tryin ' ő
ő And crazy for cryin ' ő
Jesse , honey , could you give me a hand with this ?
Yeah , okay , uh , just a second .
Thanks , sweetface . I owe you one .
- Yeah . - ő I 'm crazy for feeling ' so lonely ő
Shit !
ő I 'm crazy ő ő
- Hi . - Hi .
So , you movin ' out already ?
No such luck .
Oh , sorry .
You want me to put that in the car ?
Yeah , I 'm just , you know , taking some stuff to the Goodwill .
- It 's heavy . - Oh , yeah .
- What do you got in here ? - Oh , you know . A little of this , a little of that .
Stuff that 's gone out of style .
You ever look at something , and you realize you are just sick to death looking at it ?
That 's how I feel about that shit .
Here . In the trunk .
- In the trunk ? - You can do it .
Bend your knees .
Wow . You are strong . Nice muscle tone . You work out a lot ?
I 've been doing some push-ups- -
- Sorry . - No , that 's okay . Can 't hurt it . Might help .
Tiffany , where the fuck are you ?
You got some company ?
Nah , just baby-sittin ' . Foul-mouthed little fucker .
Let me help you with this .
Oh , um ...
What are you doing later on ?
'Cause I was thinking ...
maybe you and I could go get a drink or something .
That is , if you 're up to it .
- No , no. l-l can 't . - Why ?
- I 'm seeing someone . - Really ?
All the good guys are taken .
- l-l gotta go . - Okay .
Bye .
Jesse ?
- Treat her right , Jesse . - Excuse me ?
Treat her right . Never take her for granted .
It 's like my mother always used to say ,
" A woman spends all day slaving over a hot stove for a man ,
the least he can do is the dishes . "
She 's kind of a philosopher , my mother .
- Hmm . Take it easy . - See you around .
w-o-m-a-n
B-l-T-C-H .
That is incorrect . The correct spelling of " woman " is ...
W-O-M-A-N .
Shows how much you know .
- [ Door Opens ] - Yoo-hoo ! I 'm home .
Oh ! Tsk , tsk , tsk , tsk .
If you can 't play nice , I may just have to take your toys away .
I have a surprise for you . I 've been thinking about what you said ...
about wanting to get married .
Yeah ?
- I think it would do you good to settle down . - Babe , this is great !
You won 't regret it , I promise .
I 'm gonna treat you like a princess .
- What 's that ? - Your bride .
With this ring , I thee wed .
Oh , Chucky . She 's beautiful .
You are so dead .
Congratulations , Chucky .
Now , I 'm sure you two kids would want to be alone .
While there are still no leads in the murder of Officer Bob Bailey ,
evidence suggests that his death may be linked to another body ...
found earlier today .
Damien Baylock , whose real name was Howard Fitzwater ,
was dragged from the East River this afternoon .
Detective Preston , is there a connection between these two murders ?
Could be .
- Possibly . - Is this the work of a serial killer ?
- Maybe . - I didn 't say that .
No , sir , you didn 't , but what can you tell us about these murders ?
Nothing .
I can tell you that this used to be a nice rural community- -
[ Organ Sting ]
She 's alive ! Alive !
The bride of Frankenstein .
I promise to love , honor and cherish till death do us part .
You got that right .
She hate me .
We belong dead .
Give me the power , I beg of you .
Awake !
What a crock .
You son of a bitch ! What have you done to me ?
You got your wish . You 're mine now , doll .
And if you know what 's good for you ,
you are going to love , honor and obey .
I wouldn 't marry you if you had the body of G.I. Joe .
Hey , Raggedy Ann , you looked in the mirror lately ?
Now 's not the time to get picky . Hmm .
[ Growls ]
Face it , Tiff .
You need me . Otherwise , you 're stuck like this for good .
I don 't need you . I 'll look it up myself .
Oh , go ahead . Chapter six .
Page 217 .
The Heart of Damballa . What 's that ?
An amulet .
We need it to transfer our souls into human bodies .
Okay . And where the hell is it ?
I was wearing it around my neck ...
the night those bastards gunned me down .
It was buried with my corpse in Hackensack , New Jersey .
- All right , let 's go . - Sure . I 'll steer and you can work the pedals .
We 're dolls , you dope !
Oh , my God ! What are we gonna do ? [ Crying ]
Ay-yi-yi .
- Shut up . - You shut up .
I don 't get it . Why don 't you just mail the dolls ?
[ Tiffany ] These dolls are very special .
What do you mean , " special " ?
I mean there 's 500 bucks in it for you if you get ' em there by tomorrow .
No questions asked .
I 'd do it myself , but I have to take care of a friend ...
who 's mentally incapacitated .
Yeah .
Yeah , I 'll do it .
But I want a thousand .
Okay , sweetface , I can give you half now ,
and my friend in Jersey will give you the rest .
ő ő [ " Call Me " ]
ő Color me your color , baby ő
ő Color me your car ő
ő Color me your color , darlin ' ő
ő I know who you are ő
ő Come up off your color chart ő
ő I know where you 're coming from ő
- ő Call me ő - ő Call me ő
ő On the line ő
ő Call me , call me any , anytime ő
- ő Call me ő - ő Call me ő
ő My love , you can call me any day or night ő
ő Call me ő
Wow !
Barbie , eat your heart out .
Uh ... um- -
- Just act natural . - Right .
- ő Call me ő - ő Call me ő
ő My love , call me , call me any , anytime ő
ő My love , call me , call me for some overtime ő
" Please deliver dolls to caretaker 's office .
Forest Creek Cemetery . Hackensack , New Jersey .
Love and kisses , Tiffany . "
Cemetery ?
ő Call me for your lover 's lover 's alibi ő
- ő Call me ő - ő Call me ő
ő On the line , call me call me any , anytime ő ő
David , you remember when you were seeing Brad Barker ?
Oh ! Vividly . Whoo !
You loved him , didn 't you ?
Yeah ... I did .
What happened ?
His mother found a letter I 'd written him .
She freaked , and we haven 't spoken since .
You know , Jade ,
we get very few chances in life to be happy .
You gotta grab the brass ring when you can .
We don 't have time for this shit .
- Jade , I need to talk to you . - Hey , Jesse .
- Hey , David . - I want details .
Jesse , Warren will be home any second. lf he catches you- -
- You know I 'll never take you for granted . - Jesse- -
Like if you 'd cook , I 'd do the dishes , right ?
- What are you talking about ? - I 'd do anything for you , anything at all .
You know that , right ?
- Right ? - [ Scoffs ]
- Yes . Yes , I know . - Then marry me .
- What ? - Marry me .
Tonight .
- Warren would kill us . - I don 't care about Warren .
- That 's why we 're gonna disappear . - Where are we gonna go ?
- Anywhere you want . - Well , what are we gonna do for money ?
I got money .
- Where did you get this ? - You know my neighbor , Tiffany ?
She 's paying me $ 500 to take a couple of dolls to a friend of hers in Jersey .
Jade , there 's another 500 when we get there .
Oh , shit , Jesse . What has that freak gotten you into ?
[ Jesse ] I don 't know . I don 't care .
I can put a deposit on an apartment . I 'll get a job .
I 'll help put you through college .
I think I 'm gonna throw up .
Jade , marry me .
What do you say ?
I say I do .
- Come on . Let 's get you packed . - Okay .
Aw , that 's so romantic .
I give them six months , three if she gains weight .
[ Phone Dialing ]
It 's me .
His van is parked right in front of my house as we speak .
[ Beep ]
Who the hell is this bozo ? What 's he doing ?
Screwing with our ride , that 's what .
Ah , what the hell . I need the exercise .
Were you born with that knife super glued onto your hand , or what ?
- What are you talking about ? - For God 's sake , Chucky , drag yourself into the ' 90s .
Stabbings went out with Bundy and Dahmer .
You look like Martha Stewart with that thing .
- Who the fuck is Martha Stewart ? - My idol .
And what does Martha tell you to do when guests drop by for dinner ...
and you haven 't had time to shop ?
You improvise .
What about- -
Predictable .
Hmm ...
Uh ...
Aha .
[ Tiffany Laughing ]
Who 's there ?
[ Laughing ]
Ugh !
- Now ! - [ Gasps ]
[ Screams ]
Why does that look so familiar ?
See ? Now , that 's the work of a true homicidal genius .
- Not bad , for an amateur . - [ Door Opens ]
Shit . Here they come .
- [ Jesse ] Yeah ! - [ Jade Laughing ]
- What do we do with him ? - I don 't know .
What would Martha Stewart do ?
[ Laughing Continues ]
Here .
- [ Chucky ] Come on . Help me . - I am helping . He 's heavy .
Wait .
Huh ?
What 's the matter ?
- I could 've sworn that door was locked . - Come on . We have to go .
[ Engine Starting ]
Oh , yeah !
ő ő [ Rock ]
ő Give it back ő
ő My , my ő
Shit !
ő I 'm empty ő
- ő And sad ő ő - [ Siren Chirps ]
Now what ?
How you kids doing tonight ?
Going somewhere ?
Will you both get out of the van now , please ?
Officer Norton , I have a question .
All this following us around- -
Is that covered by your regular salary ?
- Or does my uncle pay you extra ? - Extra .
Look , I 'm sure you 're not a bad person .
I know that you 're just doing your job .
But couldn 't you just please give us a break ?
I wish I could . You seem like really nice kids .
It 's nothing personal , at least on my part .
But ... the money .
- You 're disgusting . Shut up ! - [ Laughing ]
Shut up , or I swear to God , I 'll fucking vaporize you !
[ Crowd Oohing ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Inhaling ]
- Ahh ! - [ Gasps ]
Come on . Take it easy .
- Take it easy . Come here . - We 're never gonna get away with this .
They 're never gonna let us go .
It 's gonna be okay . All right ?
Now , why don 't you go get us something to eat for the road ,
and I 'll deal with Needlenose .
- All right ? - Okay .
Ugh !
Ah !
Oh , that 's bullshit !
- You know this isn 't mine . - You 're in a lot of trouble , kid .
Now don 't you fucking move .
Shit ! Shit !
Figures you 'd hitch us a ride with the Fugitive .
Give me your lighter .
- What are you doing ? - Improvising .
Now , sit back and learn from the master .
- [ Woman ] Chief Kincaid isn 't answering . - What ? I just talked to him .
[ Woman Talking , Indistinct ]
Rude fucking doll .
Come on , Jade .
- [ Sniffs ] - Norton ?
- Are you still there ? - [ Coughs ]
- Norton ! - Bye ! - [ Tiffany Laughing ]
[ Screams ]
[ Crowd Screaming ]
Jesse !
Get in !
There they are ! Call the police !
Shit ! Shit ! Go !
Jesse , drive ! Go !
Go !
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Horns Honking ]
Well , at least you haven 't forgotten how to show a girl a good time .
Where were you ?
- Is that all you have to say ? - What do you want me to say ?
I should think you 'd have something to say about what happened back there .
I got something to say . I think you 're fucking crazy .
I 'm crazy ? You say you 'd do anything for me , and this is what I get ?
You don 't think that I had anything to do with that explosion back there ?
- Didn 't you ? - No .
To be honest , I was thinking the same thing about you .
How could you think that ?
You announced in front of a hundred people that you wanted to vaporize him .
- Oh , it was a figure of speech . - [ Phone Ringing ]
You were just as quick to accuse me .
- Hello . - What the fuck !
David , I don 't know what the hell is going on around here .
The cops think it 's all cut-and-dried .
Think of Mickey and Mallory , Bonnie and Clyde . You get the picture ?
Mickey and Mallory ? Bonnie and Clyde ? They were mass murderers , David .
Multiple murderers , actually . Mass murders happen all at once , like at the post office .
Multiple murders are serial killings .
Am I missing something ? Norton was just one murder , right ?
They found a cigarette lighter next to Norton 's car .
Belonged to that cop who got his throat slashed .
And there 's another thing . Jade , your uncle 's missing .
- What ? - I know you two had nothing to do with this .
But maybe you should turn yourselves in until they figure it out .
David , are you whacked ? Nobody is gonna believe us .
They 're setting up roadblocks at the border .
- You two had better lay low for a while . - Thanks .
[ Beep ]
Did you see Warren tonight ?
Not since this morning .
- Did you ? - No .
- [ Both Chuckling ] - ő ő [ Rock ]
ő Our little room on Seventh street is getting cold ő
ő I saw a pattern on a blanket just the other day ő
ő It looked just like the pillow you threw away ő
ő Uh-huh ő
ő I just woke up the other night ő
ő And now I know what to do I guess I 'll see you in hell ő
ő Yeah ő ő
- What are you doing ? - Do you trust me , Jade ?
Of course I do .
- [ Door Slams ] - ő ő [ " Wedding March " ]
Sucker .
I think they make a cute couple .
And if you ask me , it 'd be a shame to break ' em up ,
if you know what I mean .
[ Man ] Dearly beloved ,
we are gathered here tonight ...
to celebrate the union of two people in holy matrimony .
And what God joins together ,
let no man tear asunder .
[ Woman ] Violence in movies and television- -
- What is this shit ? - Never mind-
ő ő [ Rock ] - Jesus , the music scene 's gone to hell since I 've been dead .
- ő ő [ Heavy Metal ] - That 's more like it .
ő ő [ Continues ]
[ Tiffany ] Isn 't it beautiful ?
I always dreamed of having a big church wedding ...
with bridesmaids and a cake and my picture in the paper .
Not just the usual mug shot , but something really flattering .
Tiff ...
I 'm sorry .
For everything .
Um , I guess I can 't complain .
I mean , I always wanted us to spend more time together ,
maybe do some traveling and see the world .
Well , just look at us now .
[ Both Laughing ]
Yeah . Life sure is full of surprises .
[ Screams ]
- [ Screams ] - [ Screams ]
Stop him !
- Kill him ! - [ Grunts ]
For better or worse ,
for richer or poorer ,
in sickness and in health ,
- till death do you part . - [ Flesh Squishing ]
Congratulations . You may now kiss the bride .
Huh ?
- A true classic never goes out of style . - That was good .
[ Woman ] Is it true that Jesse and Jade may in fact be the serial killers ...
that you 've been tracking for the past few days ?
We can 't confirm that at this time .
The previous murders appear to be the work of just one killer .
It 's possible , actually- - it 's possible that one of them is a hostage ...
or simply unaware of what the other is up to .
Detective ?
For the time being , in the absence of any other information ,
these kids have to be considered armed and extremely dangerous- -
[ Sound Off ]
First thing tomorrow morning , we deliver the dolls .
We collect our money .
- We 're gonna need it . - [ Door Opens ]
Oh ! Excuse me . The , uh , door was open .
I didn 't realize there was anybody in here . Russ !
I thought we were getting a suite .
[ Roaring ]
Whoa . Who 's this ?
- I thought we were getting a suite . - No . This is our room .
Oh . [ Laughing ]
Oh !
Russ !
Look . Have you ever seen anything so cute in your whole life ?
What a great idea for a wedding gift . She 's beautiful .
Oh .
Well , this little guy has a face only a mother could love .
Hi . I 'm Chucky , and I wouldn 't talk if I were you .
Hi-de-ho .
Chucky ! Of course . I remember . He was a Good Guy doll .
- They were programmed to say all kinds of shit . - Ooh .
Well , I don 't like him at all .
You know , you two make a really delicious-looking couple .
- Hey , Diane , don 't you think ? - Oh , absolutely .
I mean , imagine what their children are gonna look like , huh ?
Listen , it 's getting late , and- -
So , what are you guys up to tonight ? Hmm ?
- [ Jade ] It 's our wedding night . - What are you watching TV for ?
Well ...
you see , it 's our wedding night as well ,
which is what makes this just so perfect .
You know what they say : The more , the merrier .
Okay , yeah . No .
You know what ? We 're really tired . Gotta get to bed early .
- Well , we 'll be right next door . - Okay .
- [ Indistinct Chatter ] - That thieving slut .
She doesn 't deserve to wear that ring .
- To us . - Oh , Russ , give me a break .
We are , technically , on our honeymoon , remember ?
Yeah , well , it was your idea to come here , not mine .
I told you we 'd have seen more action at Club Med .
- [ Gasps ] - Come on , we 're here . Let 's make the best of it .
[ Both Laughing , Moaning ]
Ooh ! [ Laughs ]
[ Moaning , Laughing Continue ]
- [ Diane Moaning ] - [ Russ ] Yeah , baby , come on ! Yeah , come on !
[ Whimpering ]
Huh ?
[ Both Scream ]
I love you .
I should have asked you this a long time ago .
Tiffany , will you be my bride ?
Oh , Chucky .
Yes . Yes !
[ Grunting ]
[ Grunts , Chuckles ]
[ Continues Grunting ]
[ Chuckles , Grunts ]
Ah !
[ Laughs ]
[ Gasps ] Oh !
Chucky !
[ Weeping ]
Why are you crying ?
I always cry at weddings .
Oh , my God ! I 'm crying !
I wonder if all the plumbing works .
Well , I don 't know about you ,
but I 'm starting to feel like Pinocchio here .
Ohh !
I am anatomically correct , ya know .
[ Moaning ]
[ Both Moaning ]
Oh ! Oh ! Wait . Wait .
- What ? What ? - Have you got a rubber ?
- Have I got a rubber ? - Yeah .
- Tiff ! - What ?
Look at me . I 'm all rubber .
Oh , that 's right . Wait .
l-l thought you were plastic .
- Tiff . - What ?
- Kiss me . - Okay .
[ Telephone Rings ]
Hello ?
- David , it 's me . - Jade !
- Where are you ? - Niagara .
The Honeymoon Sweets motel ,
which , believe me , is even worse than it sounds .
- Are you okay ? - No . I 'm married .
- Is that bad ? - I 'm really scared .
I think maybe he did it , David .
- I think Jesse has totally lost it . - Jesus .
[ Sighs ] What should I do ?
- Are you sure ? - Pretty sure .
Then you 've got to go to the police .
I don 't think I can .
I still love him .
Is that wrong ?
- [ Beeps ] - Hold on a second .
- [ Beeps ] - Hello ?
- David , it 's me . - Hey ! Jesse !
I 'm sorry to call you so late . I got a problem . It 's Jade .
Listen to me . Go to the police .
Now , before somebody else gets hurt .
Yoo-hoo ! Anybody here ?
Housekeeping !
[ Sighs ] Hello ? Housekeeping .
Joy to be here .
Okay . Oh , my goo- -
Newlyweds . [ Chuckles ]
What the heck went on here ? [ Humming ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Continues Screaming ]
[ All Screaming ]
- Oh , I can 't do this . - What ?
l-l can 't go with you , Jesse .
Not anymore .
[ Sighs ] Oh , man , I 'm glad you said that first .
- Why ? - Jade , this is too much for me .
I love you . I will always love you .
But there is a limit to how much I can take .
Would you please stop talking to me like I 'm the one who 's crazy ?
- You 're the crazy one ! You 're the mass murderer ! - You mean " multiple murderer . "
- So you admit it ? - No , I don 't !
I can 't take this shit anymore ! [ Screams ]
Anyway , the thing that struck me ...
was how sure you both sounded .
And to me , that meant one of three things- -
one of you is lying , both of you are wacko ,
or both of you are wrong .
Add to that the fact that I know you both better than anybody else ,
and I 've never seen either of you so much as hurt a fly ,
and I 've concluded that what we have here ...
is a terrible misunderstanding .
Do you guys smell something in here ? [ Sniffing ]
[ Jesse ] Okay , for the sake of argument , if it wasn 't you ...
and it wasn 't me , then who else would want to kill Warren and Needlenose ?
And those people from last night .
You 're assuming Warren 's dead . He 's only missing .
- You 're suggesting that Warren- - - Yes ! Why not ?
I 'd buy him as a psychopath before either of you two .
Pooh ! Something really stinks in here .
I told ya not to leave your dirty socks back there .
Honey , this ain 't no dirty socks . [ Sniffing ]
[ Gasps ]
- I feel like such an idiot . - Me too .
[ Jesse ] I mean , l-l can 't believe I actually thought that you could kill someone .
[ Jade ] I know . I 'm so sorry .
David , what would we do without you ?
What do you mean , " without me " ?
I mean you set us straight . We owe you one .
- You 're a good friend . The best . - [ Cocks Gun ]
Pull over ! Pull over now !
[ Tires Screeching ]
David , come on , buddy , it 's me . Come on , let 's talk this over .
- I 'm not your buddy . - Fuck , David ! Please put the gun down !
- Why ? So you can kill me too ? - We didn 't kill anybody !
Oh , you 're good . You 're good ! You even had me fooled .
- What are you talking about ? - This !
[ Both Gasp ]
You son of a bitch !
- David , I didn 't do it . She did it ! - I would never- -
Shut up ! Shut up !
Hey , help ! Over here !
- [ Siren Blares ] - Nobody move !
[ Gasps ] Oh , my God !
[ Horn Blares ]
- [ Screaming ] No ! - [ Brakes Screeching ]
That works too .
Get this heap of shit moving ! Now ! Now ! Now !
[ Siren Wailing , Tires Screeching ]
[ Cackling ]
I imagine at this point you two must have a lot of questions .
You do know who I am ?
- Chucky . - And this is Tiffany .
I believe we 've already met , haven 't we , sweetface ?
S-So h-how did you end up like this ?
- Well , it 's a long story . - It sure is .
In fact , if it was a movie , it would take three or four sequels just to do it justice .
What are you gonna do with us ?
- Funny you should ask . - These bodies are okay .
But they 're like apartments that we 're just renting .
- But now we 're movin ' on up . - Like George and Weezy .
- [ Tiffany ] And we 're lookin ' to buy . - And you know ...
what they say about real estate- -
location , location , location .
Well , you guys are definitely in the right place ...
- at the wrong time . [ Giggles ] - [ Giggles ]
[ Man On Radio ] This is a special report .
The Jesse and Jade case keeps getting weirder and weirder .
Fingerprints discovered at two separate crime scenes ...
have been identified as belonging to ...
Charles Lee Ray , the notorious serial killer gunned down in 1988 .
Now police confirm that Ray 's corpse ...
will be exhumed from a Hackensack , New Jersey , cemetery sometime today .
- What ? - Chucky , the Heart of Damballa !
- I know ! - What 'll we do ? What 'll we do ?
Shut up ! Just let me think , okay ?
First we gotta get some new wheels .
Every cop within 500 miles is lookin ' for this van .
We need something inconspicuous ,
but with a little style .
Hold still , honey , or I 'm gonna poke you in the eye again .
[ Tiffany Humming ]
Yes . I believe I 'm going to look absolutely ravishing .
[ Bell Dings ]
[ Continues Humming ]
[ Gasps ] 'Scuse me .
[ Humming ]
Nobody makes Swedish meatballs like you , babe .
- Peachy ! - Thanks , honey pot .
- I hope you left room for dessert . - You know it , pooky .
You know , if I had known that marriage was such a great gig ...
I would never have waited this long to tie the knot .
On the other hand , she 's not much of a housekeeper , is she ?
- [ Chucky ] Tiff ? - Huh ?
Those dishes aren 't gonna wash themselves , you know .
You were nice enough to cook for him .
The least he could do is wash the dish .
- What are you doin ' ? - [ Yells ]
- What would Martha Stewart say ? - Fuck Martha Stewart !
Martha Stewart can kiss my shiny plastic butt !
Here I am slaving away over a hot stove ,
making cookies , making Swedish meatballs , and for what ?
For a man who doesn 't appreciate me !
For a man who can 't even wash one fucking dish !
For a man who isn 't even a man at all where it counts ,
if you get my drift .
Take it from me , honey . Plastic is no substitute for a nice hunk of wood .
I didn 't hear her complaining last night .
Any guy would need a hunk of plastic- - probably battery-operated- -
to get a reaction out of you in bed .
And by the way , where the hell did you learn to bake ?
How dare you speak to me that way !
- You started it ! - I did not !
- [ Groans ] - No !
- [ Screams ] - [ Groans ]
- [ Tires Squealing ] - Whoa !
Jesse ! Jesse , please ! Please ! Oh , God !
[ Whimpering ] Jesse ?
[ Metal Screeching ]
- [ Whimpering ] - [ Screeching Continues ]
[ Screaming ]
- Get me out of here ! - [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Stops ]
- [ Screaming ] - You bitch !
- [ Screaming ] - [ Growling ]
Jade !
Hurry !
- Go , go , go ! - Not without you !
I 'll be right behind you !
- Hey , beautiful . [ Gun Cocks ] - [ Screams ]
[ Tiffany Moaning ]
Aah !
Jade !
- Move it ! - [ Yells ] Ow !
Ow ! Ow ! Ow ! Oh , ow ! Ow , ow , ow !
[ Dirt Being Shoveled ]
- [ Gunshot ] - [ Screaming ]
Get down there . Move !
Open the coffin , Jade .
[ Whimpering ]
- Hurry up ! - I 'm trying , you fucking midget !
- [ Gunshot ] - [ Screams ]
- [ Squeaking ] - Ugh !
You really didn 't need to see that .
Give me the amulet !
[ Grunts ] Bitch !
- You broke my neck ! - [ Screams ]
[ Thunderclap ]
- Let her go ! - Let Jade go first !
[ Chucky ] Get movin ' .
And Jade ? See ya real soon .
Get out of here .
Why can 't I ever get it on with the real good guys ?
You 're a lucky girl .
[ Sobbing ]
Catch me , Chucky . [ Moans ]
[ Coughing ]
Ugh !
- Aah ! - [ Groans ]
- God , no ! - Pull it out .
- [ Whimpering ] - [ Groaning ]
I 'll take that .
It 's show time !
[ Chucky Chanting in Foreign Language ]
Give me the power , I beg of you !
[ Chanting in Foreign Language ]
[ Chanting Continues ]
- This is it . - I love you , Chucky .
I know .
We belong together ... forever .
Kiss me .
- Hah ! - [ Screams ]
[ Groaning ]
Why ?
Oh , Chucky , look at us .
Don 't you see ? We belong dead .
Good-bye , darling .
I 'll see you in hell .
[ Sighs ]
- [ Growling ] - [ Yells ]
[ Both Grunting , Groaning ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Screaming ]
My mother always told me ...
love would set me free .
Get off my knife !
[ Rats Squeaking ]
[ Screaming ]
Let me see your hands !
- Drop the gun ! Drop it ! - [ Chucky Screaming ]
Let me out ! Let me out ! Let me out ! Let me out !
- [ Yelling ] - Whoa .
- [ Bellowing ] - [ Whimpers ]
- Don 't move ! - [ Thunderclap ]
Go ahead and shoot .
I 'll be back . I always come back !
Yeah , but dying is such a bitch .
[ Groaning ]
No one 's ever gonna believe this . You know that ?
What 's gonna happen to us ?
[ Cell Phone Rings ]
- [ Beeps ] - Preston . Yeah , I 'm here now .
I 'm afraid we 've got another corpse to add to the list .
Jesse and Jade ?
Hell , they didn 't do it .
Just get Forensics down here .
You 're never gonna fuckin ' believe this .
Right .
You two go on home . And stay put .
Let 's go home .
Ooh .
Jesus .
- [ Screaming ] - [ Screaming ] Goddamn !
- [ Screeching ] - Son of a bitch !
Holy- -
[ Wailing ]
Bitch ! Jesus !
- [ Screaming ] - [ Continues Wailing ]
[ Bawling ]
ő ő [ Rock Beat ]
[ Man ] ő Here 's to my mother ő
ő From her tribe I have crawled ő
ő Get on my feet I walk three steps then I fall ő
ő Don 't try to save me , mama Don 't kiss my wounded knees ő
ő I won 't go home now , mama Don 't make a fool of me ő
ő You see I am the boogie-woogie king ő
ő Yes , yes ő
ő Take my hand Take my other hand ő
ő Take my hand ő
ő Boogie-woogie king from the mountaintop ő
ő Is what I am ő
ő The boogie-woogie king from the mountaintop ő
ő The people watch me ride this wicked mule ő
ő From its stall ő
ő Into the streets where a thousand eyes stare at all ő
ő What do you see now , mama ő
ő This wicked mule and me ő
ő Or do you see a child try to get a gal to leave ő
ő See , I am the boogie-woogie king ő
ő Yes , yes ő
ő Take my hand Take my other hand ő
ő Take my hand ő
ő Boogie-woogie king from the mountaintop ő
ő Is what I am ő
ő Yes , the boogie-woogie king from the mountaintop ő
ő Boogie-woogie king from the mountaintop ő ő
ő Boogie-woogie king from the mountaintop ő
ő Is what I am ő ő
We belong dead .
ő Abductions and mass torture ő
ő Create emotions of vengeance ő
ő When the living become the dead ő
ő Home invasion ő
ő Private party of thieves ő
ő Blood spilled material thrill ő
ő A sign of the times ő
ő Self-destruction ő
ő A human disease ő
ő Jealousy killed the queen Sliced her neck from ear to ear ő
ő Money and power set the king free ő
ő A jury of his peers let him be ő
ő Jealousy killed the queen Sliced her neck from ear to ear ő
ő Money and power set the king free ő
ő A jury of his peers let him be ő
ő Jealousy killed the queen Sliced her neck from ear to ear ő
ő Money and power set the king free ő ő
Self-destruction . Self-destruction .
That 's more like it .
[ Sarcastic Laughing ]
" ThE EnD "